ecns.cn 2014-11-21

# Privacy Policy - Headlines, stories and photos from ecns.cn

This privacy policy applies to information we collect from all sources in connection with the Ecns.cn Website, our mobile sites, and applications that link to this Privacy Policy.

**The Information We Collect**

We may seek to collect from you various forms of personal information, including name, address, email address, telephone number, and interests in and use of products, programs and services.

We, our third-party service providers, advertisers and partners may collect various types of non-personally identifiable information. The information may include: Internet protocol address, type of operating system you are using, type of mobile device used to view this site, location information, and the content and advertisements you have accessed.

When you engage with our content through social networking sites, plug-ins or applications, you may allow us to have access to certain information from your social media profile and non-personally identifiable information from your interaction with our content.

**How We Use the Information**

We use the information that we collect to provide and manage our services, to improve the design and content of our sites, to deliver relevant marketing messages and advertisements, and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

We are committed to protecting your information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.

We use the information only for purposes of carrying out the services. However, we may share your personal information when permitted or required by law. Non-personally identifiable information may be aggregated for data statistical purposes, such as number of estimated total users or software downloads.

**Contact us**

For questions or concerns regarding our Privacy Policy, you may write to

en@chinanews.com.cn.

**Updates and Effective Dates**

We may revise our Privacy Policy periodically. Please look at the effective date at the bottom of this Privacy Policy to see when it was last revised.
